<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Estates Scanner</string>

    <string name="default_notification_channel_id" translatable="false">fcm_default_channel</string>
    <string name="login">تسجيل دخول</string>
    <string name="sorry">عذراُ</string>

    <string name="table">طاولة</string>
    <string name="discard">الغاء</string>
    <string name="location_settings">اعدادات الموقع</string>
    <string name="settings">الاعدادات</string>
    <string name="gps_message_body_3">التطبيق يحتاج الى تغيير وضع الموقع إلى دقة عالية</string>
    <string name="gps_message_body_4">App Needs to Change Location Mode to High Accuracy</string>

    <string name="gps_message_body_2">التطبيق يحتاج الى تفعيل GPS من اعدادات الجهاز!</string>
    <string name="gps_message_body">خدمة GPS غير مفعلة</string>
    <string name="home">Home</string>
    <string name="StartAnalysis">Start Analysis</string>
    <string name="about_app">About</string>
    <string name="drawer_open">open</string>
    <string name="drawer_close">close</string>
    <string name="Session">Session out</string>


    <string name="about">
The existing services for renting or buying estates enable people to compare a set of considered apartments based on the location, price, and inside conditions of the apartment. We noticed that in the real life many persons selected the apartment with a very suitable price and good inside conditions. But, once the person rented or bought the apartment some problems start to appear.
This problems are related to the surrounding environment.

For example, the nearest hospital is a little bit far from the chosen apartment, or the surrounding hospitals have a bad reputation. This can be extended to any kind of services. To bridge this gap, we propose analyzing and comparing multiple regions where the apartments located at, using a wide range of criteria. Then, the proposed system reports a set of score for each estate option. Thus, the user have a detailed report of many criteria, ours and customized ones.

These criteria are classified into many categories, i.e., noisy and pollution, services quality, artistic, environmental risk, and weather and natural risks. Each category has a set of items to be analyzed and reported. Even the customer can customize this criteria, by adding or removing. To achieve this goal, we integrating machine learning, sentiment analysis, and NLP techniques to build up the proposed system.
    </string>
    <string name="logou">Exit</string>
    <string name="LOADING">loading...</string>
</resources>
